Debajani Kashyap

■ debakashyap1901@gmail.com

9101025013

• Guwahati, Assam, India

in LinkedIn

O Instagram

Profile

Dynamic and versatile media and PR specialist with extensive experience in content creation, audio and video production, advertising, social media management, and digital marketing. Possessing a keen eye for detail and a passion for storytelling, I excel in crafting compelling narratives across various platforms to engage audiences and drive brand awareness. With a strong background in both traditional and digital media, I bring a holistic approach to communication strategies that enhance brand visibility and reputation.

Education

2022/10 - 2024/06	Master of Arts in Mass Communication and Journalism Tezpur University
2019/08 - 2022/06	Bachelor of Arts in English Literature Cotton University
2017/08 - 2019/06	Higher Secondary Cotton University

Professional Experience

2023/06 - 2023/08

India Today

Content Writer, Reporter and Videographer

- Researched and wrote stories that generated public awareness and discussion on social issues
- Managed content creation and publication process
- Intrviews numerous sources, including public officials and witnesses to uncover and report truth
- Utilized and created content for social media platforms to reach wider audiences and promote stories

2023/08 - 2023/09

All India Radio

Performer

- Recorded a voice-over for a radio spot that was broadcasted in major cities
- Performed radio drama in leading radio shows in the North East region

2020 - 2022

ETV Bharat

Voiceover artist, Translator

- Served as a voice-over artist and translator, translating American shows into Assamese and Hindi programs available for Indian citizens
- Developed and optimized content for voice search to increase visibility for voice-enabled devices
- Developed a unique and distinct voice-over style for a series of video advertisements and animated shows resulting in increase of viewership

2021 - 2022

National Film Development Corporation

Screenwriting assistant and subtitle writer

- Assistant in screenwriting and pre production for a feature film
- Translated and wrote subtitles from assamese to english

· Maintained and updated production logs to track production statistics and developed plans for film markets and festivals

2021 - 2022Pita Potata

Public Relations Executive

- Raised company profile through public relations and media campaigns, resulting in improved brand recognition and reputation
- Established a positive public image through strategic media relations and public speaking engagements
- Organized and managed public relations events, resulting in increased brand awareness and improved customer loyalty

2020 - 2021India Transformation for Education - Teach For India

Social Media Manager, Teacher

- Optimized existing content to increase visibility and engagement on social media platforms, taught underpriviledged children of NE region
- Implemented a system for tracking and reporting on team performance, providing key insights for management
- Developed a system for monitoring student progress that allowed for early intervention and timely feedback

2017 - 2018The North Eastern Chronicle

Content Creator, Event Manager and Campus Ambassador

- Created content calendars and managed content schedules to ensure timely delivery of content.
- Developed and implemented a marketing plan for a campus-wide event, resulting in increased attendance and donations.
- Collaborated with vendors and suppliers to negotiate favorable contracts that resulted in cost savings.
- · Produced promotional materials, such as flyers and posters, to increase awareness of the

Skills

Content Writing Copywriiting

News Reporting Public and Media Relations

Content Creation Videography and editing

Social Media Manager Anchoring and voice over

Graphic Design Scriptwriting

Languages

• English Assamese • Hindi

Certificates

Power of Brand Storytelling

2024

Indian Writing in English, Massive Open Online Course - Swayam 2021

National Students' Seminar on War Literature -Retracing Death, Disillusionment and Evolution

2019

Projects

2023 - 2024	Vigyan Sanchar Bi monthly magazine
2024	Legal Lens Magazine
2024	Coffee Music Film
2023	Ahalya Short Film
2023	Stay Hydrated Public Service Announcement
2023	Nature in Focus Magazine
2023	Tezpur Times News Bulletin
2022	Tumi Hahile Music Film
2021	Dadah Short Film
2021	Tales with a lid Short Film
2020	Aboddho Short Film
Portfolio	

rortiono

Portfolio link 🛮